[
    {
      "question": "Who is the CEO of HNG??",
      "choice1": "Drelcj",
      "choice2": "Xyluz",
      "choice3": "Tomisunlalude",
      "choice4": "Mark Essien",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "What other program is associated with HNG",
      "choice1": "End.ng",
      "choice2": "Begin.ng",
      "choice3": "Start.ng",
      "choice4": "Iterate.ng",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following companies is a sponsor to one of our programs",
      "choice1": "Twitter",
      "choice2": "Slackbot",
      "choice3": "Cowbell",
      "choice4": "Piggyvest",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the colour of Tomisunlalude's favourite emoji",
        "choice1": "Off-white",
        "choice2": "Pink",
        "choice3": "Black",
        "choice4": "Purple",
        "answer": 4
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the full name of Xyluz",
        "choice1": "Seyi Onirugbon",
        "choice2": "Seyi Omo-iya-Ologi",
        "choice3": "Seyi Onifade",
        "choice4": "Seyi Onifede",
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "One of the following was not a team in HNGi7",
        "choice1": "Team Falcon",
        "choice2": "Team Sentry",
        "choice3": "Team afengers",
        "choice4": "Team Incredible",
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the twitter handle of Mark",
        "choice1": "@markessien",
        "choice2": "@drelcj",
        "choice3": "@xyluz",
        "choice4": "@markesien",
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "One of these is a popular phrase in HNGi7",
        "choice1": "Sleep is for the strong",
        "choice2": "You'll never walk alone",
        "choice3": "No UEFA for chelsea next season",
        "choice4": "Sleep is for the weak",
        "answer": 4
      },
      {
        "question": "In HNGi7, if your egungun is not carefull, where will it land",
        "choice1": "Cambridge and",
        "choice2": "Badagry",
        "choice3": "Express",
        "choice4": "Way",
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is the channel for rants and bants(You'll fail this one, oooin)",
        "choice1": "Team falcon",
        "choice2": "Announcement",
        "choice3": "Random",
        "choice4": "Discussions-Mentors-Only",
        "answer": 4
      },
      {
        "question": "Wait what if i get deactivated still, what should i do?",
        "choice1": "Crry all day",
        "choice2": "Continue Learning",
        "choice3": "Sell my laptop",
        "choice4": "Wait till next 4years before i start again",
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "If you come accross this question, it is the last in my json file!",
        "choice1": "Please",
        "choice2": "Don't",
        "choice3": "Leave",
        "choice4": "Me",
        "answer": 4
      }
  ]